[
  {
    "question": "For his performance at ComplexCon 2016 in Long Beach, California, Skrillex revived his &quot;Mothership&quot; set piece for one night only.",
    "userAnswer": "True",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_24c0i07ka",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:01:14.207Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "When was Cadillac founded?",
    "userAnswer": "1964",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_24c0i07ka",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:01:21.214Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rocket League is a game which features..",
    "userAnswer": "Helicopters",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_0s27xjifr",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:01:29.423Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Rocket League is a game which features..",
    "userAnswer": "Planes",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_0s27xjifr",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:01:38.566Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "The RMS Titanic sunk during her maiden voyage from Southampton, England to which American city?",
    "userAnswer": "New York City",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_0s27xjifr",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:03:28.353Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these movies did Jeff Bridges not star in?",
    "userAnswer": "True Grit",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_0s27xjifr",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T20:03:41.256Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kramer makes a bet that he'll make what renovation to his apartment?",
    "userAnswer": "build a trash chute down the side of the building",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_ectie7rui",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T21:04:08.686Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "the letters that survive the cabin fire chronicle a torrid love affair between John Cheever and",
    "userAnswer": "Susan's father",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_ectie7rui",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T21:04:32.888Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "George's date, Natasha, thinks he blew her off because he",
    "userAnswer": "can't use the pay phone to call her",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_5dz958aq8",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T21:05:03.221Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "when Jerry and George pitch their show idea of a man who gets sentenced to being someone else's butler, the NBC executives",
    "userAnswer": "have them escorted out of the building",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_p7n8juz2q",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:39:40.765Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerry's regular barber Enzo is",
    "userAnswer": "too slow",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_p7n8juz2q",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:39:45.188Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "in an attempt to get out of a Susan Ross Foundation event, George tries to convince the Rosses that he is",
    "userAnswer": "busy renovating his parents' home",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_hn2h0qbua",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:39:57.460Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerry is arrested for",
    "userAnswer": "paying a stripper to jump out of a cake",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_hn2h0qbua",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:40:02.812Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kramer tries to get Jerry and George to invest in his business idea,",
    "userAnswer": "a pizza place where you make your own pie",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_hn2h0qbua",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:40:10.137Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "we learn that Alton Benes, Elaine's father, is",
    "userAnswer": "a railroad tycoon",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_hn2h0qbua",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:40:17.403Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "when Elaine believes her Korean manicurists are making fun of her in Korean, she",
    "userAnswer": "records their voice and hires a translator",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:40:26.389Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerry can't bring himself to kiss Margaret because she",
    "userAnswer": "was dumped by Kramer",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:40:30.892Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kramer's friend Brody points a gun at Jerry and forces him to",
    "userAnswer": "make a bootleg video",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:41:04.428Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "George tries to get his co-workers to call him \"T-Bone,\" but instead he gets the nickname",
    "userAnswer": "Koko",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:41:14.034Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Elaine and Kramer use the meat slicer to",
    "userAnswer": "feed the neighbor's cat under the door",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T22:41:23.690Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "George describes his relationship with the southern belle Marlene as",
    "userAnswer": "psychosexual",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T23:10:22.126Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Newman and Kramer ask Jerry if they can play Risk in his apartment because they",
    "userAnswer": "can make as much noise as they want",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_rsfypmjdj",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T23:10:27.227Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Kramer retrieves the statue for George by",
    "userAnswer": "bribing the pawn shop owner",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_ospr724p5",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T23:10:38.763Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "the letters that survive the cabin fire chronicle a torrid love affair between John Cheever and",
    "userAnswer": "Susan's father",
    "isCorrect": true,
    "sessionId": "sess_hjo6lrabq",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T23:12:58.056Z"
  },
  {
    "question": "Jerry's suede jacket has",
    "userAnswer": "shallow pockets",
    "isCorrect": false,
    "sessionId": "sess_hjo6lrabq",
    "timestamp": "2026-02-17T23:13:01.806Z"
  }
]